liveu.tv 2017-12-08

# Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting www. LiveU.tv (together with all content on the site including subdomains and other websites operated by LiveU or its affiliates ("LiveU") (the "Site")). We provide this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to explain our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this Site. This Privacy Policy forms part of the Terms of Use, available at www.LiveU.tv.

 **Introduction**

We recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us.

"Personal Information" means any information that may be used, either alone or in combination with other information, to personally identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, personal profile, a home or other physical address, an email address or other contact information.

Any information, video, image, data, text, documents, or other content posted at your direction onto a public area of the Site or a web service or network such as Twitter, Facebook, or LinkedIn that may have posts on the Site, becomes publicly published content and will be available to all users of the Site even if such content contains Personal Information. Please note that if you publish your contact information, you may receive unsolicited messages from users and visitors. We encourage you to publish only information you are sure you want to be accessible to anyone.  
Currently, we do not require you to provide Personal Information in order to have access to information available on our Site. However, in order to provide you with certain services given through the Site, you may be required to create an account ("Account") and provide us with your email address, a password that you will use for your Account and other specified information.

 **The Way We Use Personal Information**

If you submit Personal Information to us through the Site, then we will use your Personal Information to improve our services to you, contact you, and identify and authenticate any access to the Site and related services.

We may transfer your Personal Information within LiveU or to LiveU's third-party service providers, but only to provide services on the Site or to you. This information may be transferred to other countries.

We may also use your email address to send updates, news, or other information regarding our services. You may choose not to receive email of this type by sending a single email from the same account with the subject "BLOCK" to [privacy@LiveU.tv](mailto:privacy@LiveU.tv).

We may disclose your Personal Information or any information you submitted via the Site and its services if we have a good faith belief that disclosure of such information is helpful or reasonably necessary to (i) comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (ii) enforce our Terms of Use including investigations of potential violations thereof, (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud or security issues, or (iv) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of LiveU, its users, yourself or the public.

We may use Anonymous Information (as defined below) or disclose it to third party service providers, to improve our services and enhance your experience with the Site and its services. We may also disclose Anonymous Information (with or without compensation) to third parties, including advertisers and partners, for purposes including, but not limited to, targeting advertisements.  
Anonymous Information means information which does not enable identification of an individual user, such as aggregated information about the use of our Site and services.

 **Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

Some of our Site pages may utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Site user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them.

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser.

 **Choice**

You may choose whether or not to provide Personal Information to LiveU. The notices we may provide where LiveU collects Personal Information on the Site can help you to make this choice.

 **Access/Accuracy**

To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, LiveU wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. You may be enabled to check your profile and add information, delete information or correct any incorrect information we have.

 **Links to Other Sites**

Our Site may contain links to other sites. Other sites may also reference or link to our Site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites.

 **Children's Privacy**

The Site is not structured to attract children under the age of 18. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 18 years of age.

 **In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy**

In the event that LiveU is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your Personal Information is treated, transferred, or used. In any of the circumstances described in this paragraph, the information will be subject to the privacy policy of the purchaser or assignee.

 **Commitment**

Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and LiveU's Sites are constantly evolving to meet these demands. If you have any comments or questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@LiveU.tv.](mailto:privacy@LiveU.tv) While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as possible.

 **Your Consent**

By using this Site, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy and to LiveU's processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change this Privacy Policy at any time, which change will be effective 10 days following the modification. Your continued use of our Site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes.

 **Your California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of LiveU who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [caprivacy@LiveU.tv](mailto:caprivacy@LiveU.tv)  
Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer each year.
